twenty days left for me to create a business
and today I decided to invest in this idea.
sorry girls,
wanted to give information,
I'm creating a company from scratch
and I'm trying to validate my product on the market.
I'm trading a brownie for an honest opinion
whether you like it or not,
but like this
I really want your opinion to get here for you
from zero to ten.
What did you think?
Are you in size?
Are you too sweet?
OK
good thousand?
ha ha.
this one is already an expert,
more
until sale and it goes out.
I try to reverse engineer,
first i will turn on the product
to see if the crowd accepts and likes it.
very
thanks guys,
very good to know.
for now the feedbacks are being cool,
Is the brownie in size?
are the people liking it?
oh,
caião it's crazy to keep delivering
brownie for free for people?
one that the brownie didn't come out for free bro,
people are giving me feedback,
with this positive feedback
I end up using this to attract
new people and want to get to know my product.
and so
is the first step
for us to achieve a scale effect.
now that things are starting to get interesting uncle,
and if you want to find out why,
watch tomorrow,
tamo together.
sorry,
the light here is over the hour
hit with the little light bro,
broke out anyway.